{
    "subject": "resource/MediaCoder",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "MediaCoder",
    "human_readable": "The name of MediaCoder is MediaCoder.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9703230857849121,
            "question": "What is the name of MediaCoder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8047735095024109,
            "question": "What are the main features of MediaCoder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8042579293251038,
            "question": "Who developed MediaCoder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7433242201805115,
            "question": "What is the purpose of using MediaCoder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6465997695922852,
            "question": "What kind of tasks might MediaCoder perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.575139045715332,
            "question": "Is MediaCoder a software program?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5355001091957092,
            "question": "Is MediaCoder free to use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48869335651397705,
            "question": "Where can you download MediaCoder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4760531187057495,
            "question": "Are there any alternatives to MediaCoder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2824477553367615,
            "question": "Does MediaCoder support multiple file formats?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of MediaCoder is MediaCoder.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1251_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any alternatives to MediaCoder?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1251_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you download MediaCoder?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1251_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is MediaCoder free to use?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1251_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1251_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1251_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1251_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1251_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1251_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1251_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1251_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1251_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1251_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1251_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe context information provided discusses the software MediaCoder extensively, confirming its name and nature as a media transcoding tool. Therefore, the statement \"The name of MediaCoder is MediaCoder\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}